#### Contact

toniisaacs@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/toni-m-isaacs-msn-rn-bc (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing Education Nursing BLS

#### Certifications

Certified BLS/ACLS Instructor Certified Ambulatory Care Nurse

# Toni M. Isaacs MSN, RN-BC

Ambulatory Care Services Manager-Harris Health System Houston, Texas Area

## Summary

People can do great things with good leadership!

I believe that my experience as a school nurse, nursing instructor, case manager, and nursing supervisor have prepared me to be a valuable Nursing Director.

I have proficient and strong verbal and written communication skills. I enjoy working in fast-paced environments and am capable of working through stressful situations. I love to take on challenges, and come up with positive, successful solutions. As a result of my ICU experience, I have the foresight to anticipate a potential problem and make corrections before it materializes. I am able to adapt to everchanging environments, delegate, and multi-task.

It is my fundamental belief that effective teamwork will produce incredible results. I firmly believe it is important to think outside of the box and take risks when appropriate. I take pride in motivating others to always take advantage of positive opportunities especially as it relates to learning.

## Experience

Harris Health System
Nurse Manager
June 2014 - Present (6 years)
Acres Homes Primary Care Clinic

Implementing policies and procedures.

Conducts staff meetings and in-services.

Educates and updates staff on procedures and nursing interventions when needed, i.e. time management, medication administration, and infection control.

Addresses personnel issues as they arise.

Conflict resolution, overtime, assignments, physician concerns, etc. New hire orientation. Previously nurse manager of procedural support nurses which includes Radiation Oncology, Breast Imaging, and Sterile Processing.

Kaplan Test Prep NCLEX-RN Instructor March 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)

#### **CODE BLUE CPR**

Owner/Instructor 2012 - Present (8 years)

Cypress, TX

Cy-Fair School District
Registered Nurse
August 2009 - June 2014 (4 years 11 months)
School Nurse

Unitek College Nursing Instructor September 2007 - June 2009 (1 year 10 months) Taught Vocational Nursing Students

Houston ISD School Nurse October 2005 - June 2007 (1 year 9 months) School Nurse

Baptist Hospital, Kindred Hospital ICU Nurse May 2000 - October 2005 (5 years 6 months) Greater New Orleans Area

## Education

University of Texas at Brownsville

Master of Science in Nursing, Nursing Education · (2013 - 2014)

Dillard University
Bachelor of Science, Nursing · (1994 - 2000)